dumpalink.com 2008-07-24

# Privacy Policy - Dumpalink.com

### Privacy Policy

LAST UPDATED: 01/02/2007

Protecting the privacy of all of our users (�Users�, �you� or �your�) is a dedicated commitment of Dumpalink.com and all of the services brought to you by Dumpalink.com (collectively, "Dumpalink", �us� or �we�). This Privacy Policy (�Privacy Policy�), applies to all URLs and services provided under the Dumpalink name and in connection with the Dumpalink marks. It explains how Dumpalink treats personal information that we collect and receive on the Dumpalink website from our users and visitors. 

Personal information is information about you that is not otherwise available to the public. As the words imply, this information personally identifies you. Personal information may include, but is not limited to, your name, location, e-mail address, birth date, or other identifying information. 

You should be aware that this Privacy Policy applies ONLY to the Dumpalink website, the Dumpalink URLs, and the services and features provided by Dumpalink. This Privacy Policy does not apply to websites that you visit before or after us, to the other third party services featured on the Dumpalink site, or to third party advertisers or affiliates (collectively, �Third Party Services�). Please be sure to familiarize yourself with all of these Third Party Services� privacy policies. For your convenience ONLY, we have listed links to third party privacy policies for some of the parties that we do business with. However, not all Third Party Services may be listed. 

Now that you know what this Privacy Policy covers, you may have the following questions: 

**WHAT INFORMATION DOES DUMPALINK COLLECT?**

First and foremost, we DO NOT intentionally collect information from children under the age of 13. We realize that the reach of Dumpalink may be broad and we have taken steps to ensure the safety of our users or visitors. 

**General User Registration** : When you register to become a general member of a Dumpalink, we collect certain information about you. This information is your desired username, e-mail address, country and gender (collectively, "General Membership Information"). Once registered, you will have the opportunity to create your personal profile. ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOURSELF THAT YOU DO NOT WISH TO SHARE WITH THE PUBLIC SHOULD NOT BE INCLUDED ON YOUR PERSONAL PROFILE..

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information** : Dumpalink also collects non-personally identifiable information about you. Currently, upon registration, Dumpalink only collects your IP address, which cannot personally identify you. Dumpalink also complies user data in the aggregate for purposes of demographic compilations and other data that can help us enhance our user�s experience. 

**Dumpalink Community Features** : Once you register for Dumpalink, you will also have a chance, at your sole determination, to share other information about yourself via your personal profile. This information will be included on your personal Dumpalink profile and is meant for sharing with other community members of Dumpalink. You will always have the ability to change and edit this information. Further information on this is provided below. 

NOTE: Please remember that any personal information voluntarily disclosed by you through e-mail, in public-view personal profiles, public-view uploaded materials, chat rooms, message boards, or intra-site message systems, can be seen and used by others. For your safety, do not include information on your personal profile that you do not want others to know!!

**Contests / Sweepstakes** : Some contests, sweepstakes and other promotions that may appear from time to time on Dumpalink may be sponsored by other companies. These companies may seek to collect personal information from you in order to obtain entry. You can avoid providing your personal information to these companies and sponsors by not participating in these contests, sweepstakes or promotions. In any event, we encourage you to make yourself familiar with the privacy policy specific to any such event prior to your agreement to participate. Dumpalink will endeavor to conspicuously distinguish Dumpalink sponsored contests and sweepstakes from that of any third party sponsored contest or sweepstakes. 

**WHAT IS COLLECTING THE ABOVE INFORMATION?**

**Cookies** : Dumpalink places cookies on your computer to retain your individual preferences and improve your user experience on our website, as well as to tell us what features of our sites are most popular. From time to time, we randomly track what videos and user profiles our users are looking at via client-side cookies. We do this through a randomly generated username only and cannot tie this to your personal data. So in short, we do not store any personal information in cookies, nor do we use cookies to obtain any personal information from you. You can always adjust your web browser�s acceptance of cookies in your browser preferences.

Also, affiliates and advertisers, product and service providers may also use their own cookies when you interact with their sites via Dumpalink. You should be aware of this and always consult with their privacy policies. 

**Our Database** : All of the General Membership Information Information is stored in our database. Dumpalink does not use external, file-based or xml storage devises. 

**HOW DO WE USE GENERAL / DIRECTOR MEMBERSHIP INFORMATION AND NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?**

General Membership Information: Dumpalink will not distribute, sell or rent any of the personal information about you to other people or nonaffiliated companies except to enable the provision of services or products you have requested or when we have your permission to do so. 

Our advertisers will never be privy to your General Membership Information unless you permit us to give it to them so that they can provide you with products or services. 

Your e-mail address may be used by us for communications related to the Dumpalink services, including but not limited to, sending notices about new features, products, or other information of interest to you. Again, you can always opt out of receiving these notices. 

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: Our advertisers and affiliates may be provided general information or data regarding member usage patterns or interests, or other general demographic information so that they can better serve your needs and preferences. However, such disclosure will not include individually identifiable information. The collection of usage and interest information allows us to provide a constantly evolving innovative services, products, and features designed to satisfy member needs, wants and desires. 

**WHEN WILL WE SHARE OR DISCLOSE GENERAL MEMBERSHIP / DIRECTOR MEMBERSHIP INFORMATION?**

Despite our commitment to protecting your privacy, in certain circumstances, Dumpalink may disclose your General Membership Information under the following circumstances: 

(a) If required to do so by law; 

(b) Pursuant to a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: 

1) Enforce the Dumpalink Terms of Service;   
2) Respond to claims that any uploaded materials violate the rights of third-parties;   
3) Respond to your customer service requests;   
4) Comply with legal process; and/or   
5) Protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Dumpalink, its users, or the public.   
**HOW DO I EDIT MY MEMBERSHIP INFORMATION?**

All of your General Membership Information is located in your personal Dumpalink account. Your profile can be edited at any time, by logging in with your username and password, then clicking on the "Edit Profile" link on the top-right of the page. In addition, within all communications send to you from us at Dumpalink, we will always provide you with instructions for opting out from additional communication. 

**HOW DOES DUMPALINK PROTECT MY INFORMATION? (SECURITY)**

Your personal account is protected by your password, which you select. Dumpalink uses commercially reasonable efforts to protect our user data and restricts our employees access to such data, except to those who�s primary job function it is to maintain this data. Please note that apart from the commercially reasonable efforts we employ, due to conditions beyond our control, we cannot guarantee 100% security of user personal data.

**WHAT ABOUT SAFETY FOR CHILDREN?**

Again, we at Dumpalink take the online safety of children very seriously. We do our best not to allow children under the age of 13 to obtain a general membership account or director account. 

**I AM AN INTERNATIONAL USER, WHAT ABOUT MY PRIVACY?**

Dumpalink treats everyone the same. Dumpalink is owned and operated in the United States of America and our servers are located in the United States of America. Therefore, the collection of user data is governed, to the extent they exist, by United States federal and state privacy law. 

**WHAT IF DUMPALINK MAKES CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY?**

Dumpalink may periodically update this Privacy Policy. We will attempt, at our sole discretion, to notify our users of any updates to this Privacy Policy via email. However, we encourage you to periodically revisit the Privacy Policy link on the Dumpalink homepage to ensure that you are familiar with the current version. You are responsible for reviewing any revisions to this Privacy Policy, and your continued use of the Dumpalink website and services after any change to the policy constitutes your acceptance of the Privacy Policy. 

**CAN I CONTACT DUMPALINK ABOUT MY PRIVACY CONCERNS / QUESTIONS?**

YES! If you have a privacy concern regarding the Dumpalink website or this Privacy Policy feel free to write us at privacy@dumpalink.com. Alternatively, we can be reached by our postal mail address: 

Attention: Privacy Officer / Dumpalink  
840 Apollo Street, Suite 251  
El Segundo, CA 90245
